Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and subject files, 1929-1953; Series III
  - Alumni miscellaneous, 1951, undated (Box 145, Folder 70)
  - Alumni Musical Association, 1939-1949 (Box 145, Folder 70a-c)
  - Alumni Records and Clerical Bureau, Coordination of, 1941, undated (Box 145, Folder 71)
  - Alumni relations, 1938-1941, 1945 (Box 145, Folder 72-74)
  - Alumni University Day, 1929-1934 (Box 145a, Folder 75-79)
  - Alumni University Day, 1934-1942 (Box 146, Folder 80-87)
  - Alumni University Day: eve of broadcast, 1943-1944 (Box 146, Folder 88)
  - Alumni University Day, 1946-1953 (Box 147, Folder 89-95)
  - Alumni University Fund Association, 1932 (Box 147, Folder 95a)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1930-1931 (Box 147, Folder 96)
  - American Association of Museums, 1938 (Box 147, Folder 97)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1936 (Box 147, Folder 98)
  - Association of Modern Language and Linguistic Society (Box 147, Folder 98)
  - American Inter-University Institute of Investigation, 1936 (Box 147, Folder 99)
  - Angell, James Rowland, 1929-1937 (Box 147, Folder 100-102)
  - Anniversary, 250th: pictorial history, 1949-1950 (Box 147, Folder 103)
  - Appointments and Personnel Study, Bureau of, 1938-1950 (Box 147, Folder 104-105)
  - Archives, University, 1939 (Box 147, Folder 106)
  - Armistice Day, 1943 (Box 147, Folder 107)
  - Armistice Day, 1946-1952 (Box 147, Folder 108)
  - Art Gallery and School of Fine Arts, 1937-1941 (Box 147, Folder 109-112)
  - Art Gallery and School of Fine Arts, 1942-1953 (Box 148, Folder 113-118)
  - Art Museum Directors Association, 1934-1935 (Box 148, Folder 119)
  - Arts, Gallery of, 1935-1937 (Box 148, Folder 120)
  - Assembly: Freshman, 1939-1942 (Box 148, Folder 121-124)
  - Assembly, [University], 1943 July 4-1944 November 3 (Box 148, Folder 125-129)
  - Assembly [Freshman], 1945 March 1 (Box 148, Folder 130)
  - Assembly [Freshman], 1945 July 4 (Box 148, Folder 131)
  - Assembly [University], 1945 November 2 (Box 149, Folder 132)
  - Assembly [Freshman], 1946 March 2 (Box 149, Folder 133)
  - Assembly [University], 1946 September 12-1948 September 17 (Box 149, Folder 134-136)
  - Assemblies, 1949-1952 (Box 149, Folder 137)
  - Assemblies: miscellaneous (Box 149, Folder 138)
  - Association of American Universities and Graduate Schools, 1947-1953 (Box 149, Folder 139)
  - Association of Colleges in New England, 1937-1938 (Box 149, Folder 140)
  - Associations, Congresses, societies: programs of meetings, 1936 (Box 149, Folder 141)
  - Athletic Association, 1931-1950 (Box 149, Folder 142-151)
  - "Athletics at Yale", 1945 (Box 149, Folder 152)
  - Audio Visual Center, 1950-1953 (Box 149, Folder 153)
  - B, 1929-1936 (Box 150, Folder 154-160)
  - B, 1936-1943 (Box 151, Folder 161-167)
  - B, 1943-1952 (Box 152, Folder 168-176)
  - Baccalaureate services, 1930-1953 (Box 153, Folder 177-179)
  - Battell Chapel [with architectural plans], 1946 (Box 153, Folder 180)
  - Battell Chapel: organ concerts, 1950-1953 (Box 153, Folder 181)
  - Battell Chapel Memorial: dedication, 1947 (Box 153, Folder 182)
  - Bergmann, Werner, 1942 (Box 153, Folder 183)
  - Bible service: revised standard version, 1952 (Box 153, Folder 184)
  - Bibliographies, faculty: requests, 1939-1952 (Box 153, Folder 185)
  - Block Foundation, 1929-1930 (Box 153, Folder 186)
  - Blue Cross, Connecticut, 1949-1951 (Box 153, Folder 187)
  - Broadcasting, 1936-1940 (Box 153, Folder 188-190)
  - Broadcasting, 1940-1945 (Box 154, Folder 191-193)
  - Browder, Earl, 1939-1940 (Box 154, Folder 194)
  - Buckley, William F.: re: God and Man at Yale, 1950-1952 (Box 154, Folder 195)
  - Building charges, 1941-1942 (Box 154, Folder 196)
  - Buildings, use of, 1930-1936 (Box 154, Folder 197-203)
  - Buildings, use of, 1936-1942 (Box 155, Folder 204-211)
  - Buildings, use of, 1942-1950 (Box 156, Folder 212-219)
  - Buildings, use of, 1950-1953 (Box 157, Folder 220-222)
  - Buildings, survey of fraternity, 1943 (Box 157, Folder 223)
  - Bulletin Series #35, 1939-1940 (Box 157, Folder 224)
  - Bulletin Series #36, 1939-1941 (Box 157, Folder 225)
  - Bulletin Series, 1941-1946 (Box 157, Folder 226-228)
  - Bureau of Appointments and Department of Personnel Study, 1931-1932 (Box 157, Folder 229)
  - Bureau of Appointments, 1932-1935 (Box 157, Folder 230-232)
  - Bureau of Appointments, 1935-1942 (Box 158, Folder 233-236)
  - By-Law revision memoranda appointments, [undated] (Box 158, Folder 237)
  - C, 1929-1936 (Box 158, Folder 238-244)
  - C, 1936-1942 (Box 159, Folder 245-252)
  - C, 1942-1953 (Box 160, Folder 253-262)
  - Coduceus, 1935 (Box 161, Folder 263)
  - Calendar of the University, 1933-1954 (Box 161, Folder 264-268)
  - Calhoun College: glass medallions blueprints, 1932 (Box 161, Folder 269)
  - Cannons, El Mocro, 1942-1943 (Box 161, Folder 270)
  - "Centuria" song, 1933 (Box 161, Folder 271)
  - Change of name, 1936-1940 (Box 161, Folder 272)
  - Chapel services, compulsory, [1936?] (Box 161, Folder 273)
  - Chinese Cultural Scholarships, 1946 (Box 161, Folder 274)
  - Church of Christ: Sydney Lovett, 1938-1942 (Box 161, Folder 275)
  - Cincinnati, Society of the, 1936-1938 (Box 161, Folder 276)
  - Civil Service Improvement, President"s Committee, 1939 (Box 161, Folder 277)
  - Clare Fellowships, 1938-1941 (Box 161, Folder 278)
  - Class affiliations to colleges, 1950-1952 (Box 162, Folder 279)
  - Class of 1853 fund, 1920-1937 (Box 162, Folder 280)
  - Class of 1910, 1941-1944 (Box 162, Folder 281)
  - Class Secretaries Association: material, 1936-1942 (Box 162, Folder 282)
  - Class Secretaries Association: material, 1944-1952 (Box 162, Folder 283)
  - Clerical Assistants: regulations, 1941-1942 (Box 162, Folder 284)
  - Cloister Building, 1933-1934 (Box 162, Folder 285)
  - Coleman Memorial Collection, 1938 (Box 162, Folder 286)
  - Collections of the University, 1941-1945 (Box 162, Folder 287)
  - Yale College, Committee on Course of Study, 1945-1946 (Box 162, Folder 288)
  - Yale College, Dean William C. DeVane, 1945-1947 (Box 162, Folder 289)
  - Commencement, 1930 (Box 162, Folder 290-291)
  - Commencement, 1930 (Box 163, Folder 292)
  - Commencement: Platforms, 1930 (Box 163, Folder 293)
  - Commencement, 1931-1932 (Box 163, Folder 294-299)
  - Commencement: alumni parades, 1932-1934 (Box 163, Folder 300)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1932 (Box 163, Folder 301)
  - Commencement, 1933 (Box 163, Folder 302)
  - Commencement, 1933 (Box 164, Folder 303-304)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1933 (Box 164, Folder 305)
  - Commencement, 1934 (Box 164, Folder 306-309)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1934 (Box 164, Folder 310)
  - Commencement, 1935 (Box 165, Folder 311-314)
  - Commencement: Chief Marshall, 1935 (Box 165, Folder 315)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1935 (Box 165, Folder 316)
  - Commencement, 1936 (Box 165, Folder 317-319)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1936 (Box 166, Folder 320)
  - Commencement, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 321-324)
  - Commencement: Marshals" luncheon, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 325)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1937 (Box 166, Folder 326)
  - Commencement, 1938 (Box 166, Folder 327-328)
  - Commencement: circular letters, orders, 1938 (Box 167, Folder 329-330)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1938 (Box 167, Folder 331)
  - Commencement, 1939 (Box 167, Folder 332-333)
  - Commencement: letters, programs, instructions, 1939 (Box 167, Folder 334)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1939 (Box 167, Folder 335)
  - Commencement: seating, 1939 (Box 167, Folder 336)
  - Commencement, 1940 (Box 167, Folder 337)
  - Commencement: letters, programs, instructions, 1940 (Box 168, Folder 338)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1940 (Box 168, Folder 339)
  - Commencement: seating, 1940 (Box 168, Folder 340)
  - Commencement, 1941 (Box 168, Folder 341-344)
  - Commencement, 1941-1942 (Box 168, Folder 345)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1941 (Box 168, Folder 346)
  - Commencement: seating, 1941 (Box 169, Folder 347)
  - Commencement, 1942 (Box 169, Folder 348-349)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1942 (Box 169, Folder 350)
  - Commencement: seating, 1942 (Box 169, Folder 351)
  - Commencement: Class Day Ceremony, 1942 December 18 (Box 169, Folder 352)
  - Commencement, 1942 December 19 (Box 169, Folder 353)
  - Commencement, 1943 (Box 169, Folder 354)
  - Commencement: individual schools, 1943 (Box 169, Folder 355)
  - Commencement: calendar, 1943 (Box 169, Folder 356)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1943 (Box 170, Folder 357)
  - Commencement, 1943 October (Box 170, Folder 358)
  - Commencement, 1944 (Box 170, Folder 359-360)
  - Commencement: Class Day, 1944 February 12 (Box 170, Folder 361)
  - Commencement: individual schools, 1944 (Box 170, Folder 362)
  - Commencement: Valedictory Dinner, 1944 October 19 (Box 170, Folder 363)
  - Commencement, 1945 (Box 170, Folder 364-365)
  - Commencement: class of 1945 W (Box 170, Folder 366)
  - Commencement: individual schools, 1945 (Box 170, Folder 367)
  - Commencement, 1945 October 24 (Box 171, Folder 368)
  - Commencement: platform, 1945 (Box 171, Folder 369)
  - Commencement, 1946 (Box 171, Folder 370)
  - Commencement: commemorative exercises, 1946 (Box 171, Folder 371)
  - Commencement: February, 1946 (Box 171, Folder 373)
  - Commencement: individual schools, 1946 (Box 171, Folder 374)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1946 (Box 171, Folder 375)
  - Commencement, 1947 (Box 171, Folder 376)
  - Commencement: circular letters, instructions, 1947 (Box 171, Folder 377)
  - Commencement: correspondence, 1947 (Box 172, Folder 378)
  - Commencement, 1948 (Box 172, Folder 379-380)
  - Commencement: correspondence, 1948 (Box 172, Folder 381)
  - Commencement: February, 1948 (Box 172, Folder 382)
  - Commencement: circular letters, instructions, 1949 (Box 172, Folder 383)
  - Commencement: correspondence, 1949 (Box 172, Folder 384)
  - Commencement: February, 1949 (Box 172, Folder 385)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1949 (Box 172, Folder 386)
  - Commencement: seating lists, 1949 (Box 173, Folder 387)
  - Commencement, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 388)
  - Commencement: circular letters, instructions, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 389)
  - Commencement: platforms, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 390)
  - Commencement: seating lists, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 391)
  - Commencement: Service of Remembrance, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 392)
  - Commencement: University of Pittsburgh, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 393)
  - Commencement: Woolsey Hall, rain, 1950 (Box 173, Folder 394)
  - Commencement, 1951 (Box 173, Folder 395)
  - Commencement: class dinner, 1951 (Box 173, Folder 396)
  - Commencement: Services of Remembrance, 1951 (Box 174, Folder 397)
  - Commencement, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 398)
  - Commencement information, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 399)
  - Commencement: Service of Remembrance, 1952 (Box 174, Folder 400)
  - Commencement, 1953 (Box 174, Folder 401)
  - Commencement: circular letters, instructions, 1953 (Box 174, Folder 402)
  - Commencement: seating lists, 1953 (Box 174, Folder 403)
  - Committee on Corporation Meetings, 1937 (Box 174, Folder 404)
  - Connecticut Tercentenary, 1935 (Box 174, Folder 405)
  - Convocation Ceremony, 1946 (Box 174, Folder 406)
  - Convocation Ceremony, 1946 (Box 175, Folder 407)
  - Convocation pamphlet, 1946 (Box 175, Folder 408)
  - Convocation platform, 1946 (Box 175, Folder 409)
  - Cooper Union, 1953 (Box 175, Folder 410)
  - Corinthian Yacht Club, 1943 (Box 175, Folder 411)
  - Corwith, John W., Memorial Prize, 1929-1949 (Box 175, Folder 412)
  - Cowles, Alfred, Foundation, 1943-1947 (Box 175, Folder 413)
  - D, 1929-1936 (Box 175, Folder 414-420)
  - D, 1936-1946 (Box 176, Folder 421-430)
  - D, 1946-1953 (Box 177, Folder 431-436)
  - Davis, Jerome
    - American Association of University Professors: correspondence, 1936-1937 (Box 177, Folder 437)
    - American Association of University Professors: inquiry, 1936-1937 (Box 177, Folder 438-439)
    - American Association of University Professors: material, 1937 (Box 177, Folder 440-441)
    - American Association of University Professors: report, 1937 (Box 177, Folder 442)
    - Complaints, 1931-1937 (Box 177, Folder 443)
    - Correspondence concerning, 1936-1938 (Box 178, Folder 444-446)
    - Dismissal protests, 1936 (Box 178, Folder 447)
    - Dismissal, telegram reactions to, 1937 (Box 178, Folder 448)
    - Gilbert L. Stark Foundation, 1936 (Box 178, Folder 449)
    - Henry Wright Cottage Benefit Lecture, 1933-1936 (Box 178, Folder 450)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1936 November-1938 September (Box 178a, Folder 451-457)
    - Petitions for reappointment, 1937 (Box 178, Folder 458)
    - Yale statements, 1937 (Box 178, Folder 459)
  - Day, George P., 1930-1942 (Box 179, Folder 460-461)
  - Dean"s Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 179, Folder 462)
  - Deans, letters to, 1944 (Box 179, Folder 463)
  - Degrees, 1947-1952 (Box 179, Folder 464)
  - Design Laboratory, 1952 (Box 179, Folder 465)
  - Development, University Committee on, 1946-1948 (Box 179, Folder 466)
  - Distribution of Students, 1934-1935 (Box 179, Folder 467)
  - Divinity School, 1937-1953 (Box 179, Folder 468)
  - Dormitory rules, 1935 (Box 179, Folder 469)
  - Drama, Department of, 1937-1949 (Box 179, Folder 470)
  - Dwight Hall, 1931-1944 (Box 179, Folder 471)
  - E, 1929-1938 (Box 179, Folder 472-480)
  - E, 1938-1953 (Box 180, Folder 481-488)
  - Eaton, Daniel C.: portrait, 1931 (Box 180, Folder 489)
  - Educational Planning, Committee on, 1942 (Box 180, Folder 490)
  - Eisenhowet, Dwight D., 1948 (Box 180, Folder 491)
  - Ellsworth, Oliver: portrait, 1927-1931 (Box 180, Folder 492)
  - Engineering, School of, 1932-1947 (Box 180, Folder 493)
  - Engineering Science Management Training Program [ESMT], 1942-1945 (Box 180, Folder 494)
  - England, information for students going to, 1950 (Box 180, Folder 495)
  - Entertainment, President"s Committee on, 1944-1953 (Box 180, Folder 496)
  - Examination information, 1938-1940 (Box 180, Folder 497)
  - Extracurricular activities, 1945 (Box 180, Folder 498)
  - F, 1929-1940 (Box 181, Folder 499-510)
  - F, 1940-1953 (Box 182, Folder 511-519)
  - Faculty, 1941-1942 (Box 182, Folder 520)
  - Faculty: foreign born, 1940-1942 (Box 182, Folder 521-522)
  - Faculty: invitation list for Faculty Tea, 1946-1949 (Box 182, Folder 523)
  - Faculty Club: with architectural plans, 1929-1930 (Box 182, Folder 524)
  - Faculty Club, 1931-1953 (Box 183, Folder 525)
  - Faculty Club and the president"s Committee on University Entertainment, 1942-1944 (Box 183, Folder 526)
  - Faculty Tea, 1940 (Box 183, Folder 527)
  - Farnum, Thomas W., 1938-1940 (Box 183, Folder 528)
  - Film, 1935-1949 (Box 183, Folder 529)
  - Film Society, Yale, 1939-1940 (Box 183, Folder 530)
  - Fisher, H.B. [F.B.I.], 1943-1953 (Box 183, Folder 531)
  - Fitkin Memorial Building, 1930 (Box 183, Folder 532)
  - Focal Point, 1950-1953 (Box 183, Folder 533)
  - Foreign Area Studies, 1943 (Box 183, Folder 534)
  - Foreign Students, 1940-1945 (Box 183, Folder 535-541)
  - Foreign Students, 1945-1951 (Box 184, Folder 542-545)
  - Form letters, 1930-1947 (Box 184, Folder 546)
  - Forestry, School of, 1938-1948 (Box 184, Folder 547)
  - Forty-two Club, 1943 (Box 184, Folder 548)
  - Friedman, Stanleigh, 1944-1945 (Box 184, Folder 549)
  - French guns: 75mm (Box 184, Folder 550)
  - Freshman sons, 1935-1942 (Box 184, Folder 551)
  - Freshman year: Dean Buck, 1944-1946 (Box 184, Folder 552)
  - Freshman year, 1946-1947 (Box 184, Folder 553)
  - G, 1929-1935 (Box 184, Folder 554-559)
  - G, 1935-1949 (Box 185, Folder 560-570)
  - Gibbs, Josiah Willard: centennial, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 571)
  - Graduate Studies, Hall of, 1931-1948 (Box 186, Folder 572-575)
  - Graves, Henry S., 1939 (Box 186, Folder 576)
  - Greenway Memorial, 1927-1935 (Box 186, Folder 577)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1950-1953 (Box 186, Folder 578)
  - Guide service, 1937-1939 (Box 186, Folder 579)
  - Guided tours, 1949-1950 (Box 186, Folder 580)
  - Gunnery School: arms of, 1948-1949 (Box 186, Folder 581)
  - Gymnasium, Payne Whitney, 1932-1944 (Box 186, Folder 582-585)
  - H, 1929-1936 (Box 187, Folder 586-597)
  - H, 1935-1941 (Box 188, Folder 598-607)
  - H, 1940-1953 (Box 189, Folder 608-617)
  - Hadley entry, 1933 (Box 189, Folder 618)
  - Hadley, Arthur T.: funeral of, 1930 (Box 189, Folder 619)
  - Hale, Nathan: statue, undated (Box 189, Folder 620)
  - Hall, Emily: gift fund, 1949-1950 (Box 190, Folder 621)
  - Headmasters Association, 1934-1939 (Box 190, Folder 622)
  - Headmasters Association, 1934-1939 (Box 190, Folder 623)
  - Health, Department of University, 1944-1945 (Box 190, Folder 624)
  - Health insurance, 1935 (Box 190, Folder 625)
  - Hedley, David, 1934 (Box 190, Folder 626)
  - Henry Fund, 1930-1934 (Box 190, Folder 627-633)
  - Henry Fund, 1934-1938 (Box 191, Folder 634-640)
  - Henry Fund, 1938-1946 (Box 192, Folder 641-647)
  - Historical Register, 1939 (Box 192, Folder 648)
  - Hospital seal, 1945 (Box 192, Folder 649)
  - Hospital Service Fund, 1937 (Box 192, Folder 650)
  - Housing Bureau, 1946-1947 (Box 192, Folder 651)
  - Housing: Yale-Life Housing Conference, 1939 (Box 192, Folder 652)
  - Howland Fellowship, 1948-1952 (Box 192, Folder 653)
  - Howland Prize, 1930-1934 (Box 192, Folder 654)
  - Howland Prize, 1944 (Box 192, Folder 655)
  - Howland Prize and Howland Lectures, 1930-1944 (Box 192, Folder 656)
  - Humanities, Council Committee on, undated (Box 193, Folder 657)
  - Humanities, Science and, 1947 (Box 193, Folder 658)
  - Hymnals, 1932-1934 (Box 193, Folder 659)
  - I, 1929-1953 (Box 193, Folder 660-671)
  - Immigration, 1929-1930 (Box 193, Folder 672-673)
  - Immigration, 1930-1935 (Box 194, Folder 674-682)
  - Immigration, 1934-1940 (Box 195, Folder 683-691)
  - Immigration, 1940-1947 (Box 196, Folder 692-702)
  - Inauguration, 1937 (Box 196, Folder 703)
  - Inauguration, 1937 (Box 197, Folder 704)
  - Inauguration: invitation correspondence, 1937 (Box 197, Folder 705-706)
  - Inauguration: memorabilia, 1937 (Box 197, Folder 707)
  - Inauguration: ushers, 1937 (Box 197, Folder 708)
  - Industry: Yale cooperation, 1948 (Box 197, Folder 709)
  - Information Center, 1947 (Box 197, Folder 710)
  - Information, Committee for the Dissemination of, 1951-1952 (Box 197, Folder 711)
  - International Affairs, Symposium on, 1939 (Box 197, Folder 712)
  - International Encyclopaedia: Yale information, 1930 (Box 197, Folder 713)
  - Internes and Medical Students, Association of, 1947 (Box 197, Folder 714)
  - Introduction, letters of, 1929-1950 (Box 197, Folder 715-719)
  - Introduction, letters of, 1950-1953 (Box 198, Folder 720)
  - "Introduction to Yale": correspondence, 1935 (Box 198, Folder 721)
  - "Introduction to Yale", 1935-1936 (Box 198, Folder 722)
  - "Introduction to Yale": ms, 1938-1939 (Box 198, Folder 723)
  - "Introduction to Yale": ms, undated (Box 198, Folder 724)
  - "Introduction to Yale", 1945 (Box 198, Folder 725)
  - Institute of Human Relations, 1931 (Box 198, Folder 726)
  - Invitations A-Ca, 1929-1930 (Box 198, Folder 727)
  - Invitations Ch-Il, 1929-1930 (Box 198, Folder 728)
  - Invitations In-P, 1929-1930 (Box 199, Folder 729)
  - Invitations P-Z, 1929-1930 (Box 199, Folder 730)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1930-1931 (Box 199, Folder 731-734)
  - Invitations A-R, 1931-1932 (Box 199, Folder 735-737)
  - Invitations S-Z, 1931-1932 (Box 200, Folder 738)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1932-1934 (Box 200, Folder 739-744)
  - Invitations A-Ca, 1934-1935 (Box 200, Folder 745)
  - Invitations Ch-H, 1934-1935 (Box 200, Folder 746)
  - Invitations I-O, 1934-1935 (Box 201, Folder 747)
  - Invitations P-Z, 1934-1935 (Box 201, Folder 748)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1935-1936 (Box 201, Folder 749-753)
  - Invitations A-D, 1936-1937 (Box 201, Folder 754)
  - Invitations E-Ha, 1936-1937 (Box 201, Folder 755)
  - Invitations He-Z, 1936-1937 (Box 202, Folder 756-758)
  - Invitations A-Ob, 1937-1938 (Box 202, Folder 759-763)
  - Invitations Ol-R, 1937-1938 (Box 203, Folder 764)
  - Invitations T-Z, 1937-1938 (Box 203, Folder 765)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1938-1939 (Box 203, Folder 766-769)
  - Invitations A-B, 1939-1940 (Box 203, Folder 770)
  - Invitations C-G, 1939-1940 (Box 203, Folder 771)
  - Invitations H-P, 1939-1940 (Box 204, Folder 772)
  - Invitations S-Z, 1939-1940 (Box 204, Folder 773)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1940-1941 (Box 204, Folder 774-777)
  - Invitations A-F, 1941-1942 (Box 204, Folder 778)
  - Invitations H-M, 1941-1942 (Box 204, Folder 779)
  - Invitations N-R, 1941-1942 (Box 205, Folder 780)
  - Invitations S-Z, 1941-1942 (Box 205, Folder 781)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1942-1943 (Box 205, Folder 782-784)
  - Invitations A-M, 1944-1946 (Box 205, Folder 785-788)
  - Invitations N-Z, 1944-1946 (Box 206, Folder 789-791)
  - Invitations A-N, 1946-1948 (Box 206, Folder 792-795)
  - Invitations O-So, 1946-1948 (Box 207, Folder 796)
  - Invitations Sp-Z, 1946-1948 (Box 207, Folder 797)
  - Invitations A-R, 1948-1949 (Box 207, Folder 798-802)
  - Invitations S-T, 1948-1949 (Box 208, Folder 803)
  - Invitations U-Z, 1948-1949 (Box 208, Folder 804)
  - Invitations A-Z, 1949-1950 (Box 208, Folder 805-809)
  - Invitations A-Be, 1950-1953 (Box 208, Folder 810)
  - Invitations Bo-O, 1950-1953 (Box 209, Folder 811-817)
  - Invitations P-Z, 1950-1953 (Box 210, Folder 818-822)
  - Ivy: class plantings list, 1936 (Box 210, Folder 823)
  - J, 1929-1939 (Box 210, Folder 824-833)
  - J, 1939-1953 (Box 211, Folder 834-841)
  - Japanese, 1942-1946 (Box 211, Folder 842)
  - Jepson, Harry B., 1939, 1952 (Box 211, Folder 843)
  - Johnson, Frederick B., undated (Box 211, Folder 844)
  - Johnson, Mrs. G.A., 1929-1930 (Box 211, Folder 845)
  - K, 1929-1942 (Box 211, Folder 846-858)
  - K, 1942-1950 (Box 212, Folder 859-862)
  - Kent Chemical Laboratory, 1930-1931 (Box 212, Folder 863)
  - Keogh, Andrew, 1930-1936 (Box 212, Folder 864)
  - Knollenberg, Bernhard, undated (Box 212, Folder 865)
  - L, 1929-1939 (Box 212, Folder 866-875)
  - L, 1951-1953 (Box 213, Folder 876-884)
  - Labor and Management Center, 1948-1949 (Box 213, Folder 885)
  - Lane, M.P., 1941 (Box 213, Folder 886)
  - Latin-American cultural relations, 1941-1943 (Box 213, Folder 887)
  - Latin-American relations, 1944-1948 (Box 213, Folder 888)
  - Laufer, Arthur R., 1941-1943 (Box 213, Folder 889)
  - Law School, 1935-1951 (Box 214, Folder 890-891)
  - Lecture Committee, 1939-1950 (Box 214, Folder 892-897)
  - Lectures for consideration, 1950-1953 (Box 214, Folder 898)
  - Lectures: re withholding tax, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 899)
  - Lectures
    - Beaumont, 1930-1949 (Box 214, Folder 900)
    - Bergen, 1929-1944 (Box 214, Folder 901-903)
    - Bergen, 1944-1953 (Box 215, Folder 904-908)
    - Block, 1930-1949 (Box 215, Folder 909)
    - Bromley, 1929-1953 (Box 215, Folder 910-915)
    - Dodge, 1929-1935 (Box 215, Folder 916)
    - Hoyt, 1939-1952 (Box 215, Folder 917)
    - Lamont, 1929-1953 (Box 216, Folder 918-922)
    - Liberal Studies, 1944 (Box 216, Folder 923)
    - Silliman, 1929-1953 (Box 216, Folder 924-925)
    - Storrs, 1937-1940 (Box 216, Folder 926)
    - Thomas, 1938-1939 (Box 216, Folder 927)
    - Terry, 1929-1935 (Box 216, Folder 928-933)
    - Terry, 1935-1953 (Box 217, Folder 934-943)
    - Professor Tinker, 1944-1945 (Box 217, Folder 944)
    - Trumbull, 1943-1952 (Box 218, Folder 945-948)
    - Turck, 1951 (Box 218, Folder 949)
    - Woodward, 1929-1940 (Box 218, Folder 950-954)
    - Woodward, 1940-1953 (Box 219, Folder 955-963)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929-1938 (Box 220, Folder 964-972)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1948 (Box 221, Folder 973-979)
  - Liberal Studies Research Fellowships, 1943-1944 (Box 221, Folder 980)
  - Library: letters on the Librarian appointment, 1937-1938 (Box 221, Folder 981)
  - Library and Museum Committee, 1938-1946 (Box 221, Folder 982)
  - Library, Sterling, 1936-1953 (Box 222, Folder 983-988)